Turkus, Burton B. Arbitration Files 5712
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Gourmet, H. Gles, Ltd. vs. Culinary Employees Division of Local 1115 Joint Board., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  3/9/79. Issue: Union representation - certification. Includes: Correspondence, legal documents.
- Grainger, W.W., Inc. vs. IBT, Local 814, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  10/4/78. Issue: Severance pay. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Grand Union Company vs. IBT, Local 456, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  7/16/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. IBT, Local 202, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  2/1/78. Issue: Discipline - Suspension - failure to meet standards of production. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents.
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. Butchers, Food Handlers and Allied Workers, Local 174, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  11/13/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - alcoholism. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. General Warehousemen's Union, Local 852, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  8/6/74. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Legal documents, supporting documentation, correspondence.
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. Butchers, Food Handlers and Allied Workers, Local 174, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  5/6/82. Issue: Vacation pay - termination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. IBT, Local 337, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  2/28/75. Issue: Assignment of job - rates of pay - shift work. Includes: Award only.
- Great Lakes Dredge and Dock Company vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Marine Division, Local 25, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  7/3/70. Issue: Assignment of jobs - jurisdiction. Includes: Award only.
- Greater New York Health Care Facilities Association: Hillside Manor, River Manor, Concourse Nursing Home, Kings Terrace Nursing Home; vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  7/1/79. Issue: Fringe benefits - rates of pay, welfare fund, sick benefits, vacations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Green Dolphin Restaurant vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  11/27/74. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination. Includes: Award only.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Council of Greyhound Divisions, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  4/4/77. Issue: Sick leave - disability - Doctor's Certificate. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1205, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  11/20/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules - mode of dress. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Council of Greyhound Divisions, Division 1493, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  5/2/78. Issue: Discipline - suspension - accident. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1202, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  4/22/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude -threats. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1493, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  2/26/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - accident - negligence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents
- Greyhound Lines East, Division of Greyhound Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1202, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  7/30/74. Includes: Discipline - discharge - accident. Includes: Award only.
- Group Health Insurance vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  10/24/69. Issue: Absences - excessive. Includes: Award only.
- Group Health Insurance vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  6/29/71. Issue: Applications for employment - omission of information, Includes: Award only.
- Group Health Insurance vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  6/12/73. Issue: Standards of production. Includes: Award only.
- Gulf Trading and Transportation Company vs. National Maritime Union, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  12/18/79. Issue: Disability - hiring - physical examinations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Hartz Mountain Associates vs. Hotel, Restaurant Employees Union, Local 69, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  3/16/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Improper personal conduct. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Hartz Mountain Associates vs. Hotel, Restaurant Employees Union, Local 69, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  5/3/82. Issue: Rates of pay - inequities - contract interpretation. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Hialeah Convalescent Home vs. Nursing Home and Hospital Employees, Local 1115, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  5/2/77. Issue: resolved
- Hobart Corporation vs. IBT, Local 89, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  7/11/79. Issue: Subcontracting. Includes: Legal documents, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Holiday Inn vs. Hotel, Motel, and Restaurant Employees, Local 355, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  5/12/75. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Award only.
- Home Box Office vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  5/21/82. Issue: withdrawn. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Home Lines Cruises, Inc. vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  1/16/78. Issue: withdrawn. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, briefs.
- Host International, Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  7/23/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper conduct - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, exhibits, briefs
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  1/19/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  1/18/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  4/21/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  3/31/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, briefs, correspondence.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  10/3/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  4/9/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  4/15/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  5/26/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Correspondence, briefs. No Award.
- Host Services of New York, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Includes: Miscellaneous correspondence, exhibits, regarding above cases.
- Howard Oil Company vs. UAW, Local 365, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  11/12/76. Issue: Rates of pay - fringe benefits.
- Humble Oil Company vs. Jersey Standard Tanker Officers Association, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  5/21/71. Issue: Rates of pay - negotiations - assignment of jobs. Includes: Award only.
- Hyatt House Hotel vs. Hotel, Motel and Restaurant and High-Rise Employees, Local 355, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  4/29/75 Issue: Rates of pay - past practice.
- Independent Metal Fabricators vs. UAW, Local 365, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  9/14/82. Issue: Pension and welfare payments. Includes: No award.
- Inflight Motion Pictures, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  2/5/76. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Inflight Motion Pictures, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 295, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  12/9/75. Issue: Suspension - improper job attitude. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation. No Award.
- Inflight Motion Pictures, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  4/22/76. Issue: Layoff. Includes: Arbitrator's notes. correspondence, briefs, legal documents, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Inflight Motion Pictures, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  4/21/76. Issue: Assignment of job - assignments outside of bargaining unit. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Inflight Motion Pictures, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  4/21/76. Issue: Rates of pay - increase - contract interpretation. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Inflight Motion Pictures, Inc. vs. IATSE, Local 306, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  7/1/80. Issue: Rates of pay - overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, legal documents.
- Ingra of New York vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 6, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  2/22/82. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- Inhilco, Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, Local 22, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  1/10/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Improper personal conduct. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Intercontinental Hotels Corporation vs. IBT, Local 732, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  12/8/81. Issue: Certification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 827, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  April 3, 1980. Issue: Certification - election. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Interstate United Corporation vs. Hotel, Restaurant, and Club Employees Union, Local 6, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  8/21/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence.
- Isabella Geriatric Center vs. District 1199, Drug and Hospital Union, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  11/22/76. Issue: Discipline - suspension - tardiness. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Island Hills Country Club vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  5/10/74. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. Includes: Award only.
- Island Telephone Answering Service, Inc. vs. United Telephone Answering and Communications Service Union, Local 780, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  5/6/74. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Award only.
- Japan Airlines vs. IAM, Local 151, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  4/30/81. Issue: Overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, legal documents, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Japan Airlines vs. IAM, Local 151, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  1/6/78. Issue: Rates of pay - overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits, legal documents.
- Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  4/12/76. Issue: Certification (representation election). Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- John L. Armitage and Company vs. OCAW, Local 406, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  1/26/70. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination. Includes: Award only.
- KLM Royal Dutch Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 504, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  8/30/79. Issue: Discipline - suspension - seniority. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Keene's Restaurant vs. Keene's Restaurant Employees Association, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  7/23/81. Issue: Representation certification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, briefs, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Kew Gardens General Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  5/19/77. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Keystone Shipping Company vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  8/18/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - hiring - management rights. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Kiamesha Concord Hotel, Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, Local 76, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  4/30/76. Issue: Rates of pay, holidays, sick leave. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Kimberly Knitwear vs. Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  12/17/76. Includes: withdrawn.
- Kollsman Instrument Corporation vs. IAM, District 15, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  3/27/70. Issue: Classification of jobs. Includes: Award only.
- La Guardia Hospital vs. Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union, Local 144, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  5/10/79. Issue: settled
- La Guardia Hospital vs. Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union, Local 144, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  2/7/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules - no-smoking rule. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Lan-Chile Airlines vs. IAM, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  9/5/72. Issue: Layoff - discharge - seniority - fights and altercations. Includes: Award only.
- Lauraine Murphy Manhasset Inc. vs. Culinary Employees Union, Local 1115, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  8/20/81. Issue: Rate of pay - fringe benefits. Includes: Supporting documentation, correspondence, briefs
- Lee Spring Company vs. Metal Craft Union, Local 238, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  9/4/75. Issue: Insubordination - warnings. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, briefs.
- Leeds-Dixon Laboratories, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 1518, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  2/22/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Lerner Shops of America, Inc. vs. UAW, District 65, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  11/6/80. Issue: Suspension - fights and altercations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Lerner Shops, Inc. vs. RWDSU, Local 1102, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  2/3/77. Issue: Representation - certification. Includes: Supporting documentation, correspondence, briefs.
- Lerner Stores Corporation vs. UAW, District 65, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  2/18/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Levin Fixture Corporation vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2682, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - threats. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Levin Fixture Corporation vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2682, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  7/5/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - failure to meet production standards; Strikes - slowdowns. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Levin Fixture Corporation vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2682, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  5/19/76. Issue: settled. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Long Island Jewish Hospital vs. National Drug and Health Care Union, Local 1199, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  2/24/77. Issue: settled. Includes: Correspondence, briefs
- Longchamps, Inc. vs. Dining Room Employees, Local 1, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  10/13/71. Issue: Shutdown - economic reasons - recall - rehire. Includes: Award only
- Lufthansa German Airlines vs. IAM, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  1/3/72. Issue: Contracting-out of bargaining unit work. Includes: Award only.
- Lufthansa German Airlines vs. IAM, District 100, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  9/8/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Lydia E. Hall Hospital vs. Registered Nurses Association, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  11/16/79. Issue: Probationary employees - personal and sick leave accumulation. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Lykes Brothers Steamship Company vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  10/15/79. Issue: Hiring - management rights - sex discrimination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Lykes Brothers Steamship Company vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  2/28/80. Issue: Contract modification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Manhattan Sales and Service Operations, Chrysler Corporation, vs. IBT, Local 868, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  6/1/76. Issue: Layoff - reduction in force - economic reasons -work distribution. Issue: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Marine Transport Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  1/31/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Marine Transport Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  8/11/79. Issue: cancelled.
- Marine Transport Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  9/20/79. Issue: cancelled.
- Marine Displays, Inc. vs. UAW, District 65, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  9/9/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Mary Immaculate Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  9/25/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - excessive absence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- Mary Immaculate Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  5/12/78. Issue: Rate of pay, welfare fund. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Massachusetts Electric Company vs. Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, Inc., Local 330, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  11/13/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - excessive absence - sleeping on job. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology vs. Research, Development, and Technical Employees, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 38a)
  5/12/77. Issue: ? Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs. No Award.
- Massapequa General Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  10/29/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Hearing cancelled.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Delta Steamship Lines, Inc, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  9/25/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude -general attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, exhibits
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Keystone Shipping Company, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  10/28/81. Issue: Promotions - qualifications. Includes: Correspondence, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. American Maritime Association, Maritime Service Committee and Tanker Service Committee, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  6/9/81. Issue: Fringe benefits - health and benefit plan. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Trustees, Maritime Advancement, Training, Education and Safety Program, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  3/26/82. Issue: Rates of pay - new employees. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. United States Lines, Inc., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  6/8/82. Issue: Reduction in force - termination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Prudential Lines, Inc., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  7/15/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - rules violation. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. U.S.S. Oakland, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  5/28/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - incompetence. Includes: No Award.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. United States Lines, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  12/24/81. Issue: ? Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence. No Award.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. United States Lines, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  2/24/81. Issue: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence. No Award.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Hudson Waterways Corporation and Manhattan Tankers, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  6/15/81. Issue: Transfer - notice. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Prudential Lines, Inc, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  6/22/81. Issue: Fringe benefits. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Sealand Services, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  9/25/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - incompetence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Sealand Services, Inc., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  6/9/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - safety - incompetence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Lykes Brothers Steamship Company., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  6/29/81. Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority. Includes: Supporting documentation.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Delta Steamship Corporation., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  4/8/82. Issue: Insubordination - disorderly conduct - safety. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Keystone Shipping Company., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  12/24/81. Issue: Qualifications - seniority. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, exhibits, supporting documentation. No Award.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Moore McCormack Lines., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  3/6/81. Issue: Work stoppage. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Pacific Maritime Association and Matson Navigation Company., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  4/3/81. Issue: Reduction in force - seniority. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Puerto Rico Marine Management Company, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  9/15/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - negligence and carelessness. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Sealand Services, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)